methodtreatment.com 2019-08-12

# Privacy Policy - Los Angeles Drug Rehab, Luxury Mental Health Treatment California, Dual Diagnosis Treatment Center Los Angeles, 1 Method, One Method Center, Drug detox Beverly hills, best drug recovery rehabs in West Los Angeles, top drug rehab programs in southern California, 5 star alcohol detox los Angeles area near me, top mental health treatment United States

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to 1 Method Center and all of its affiliates and related parties (collectively, the “Company”) with respect to the Company’s website and services that display or link to this notice. This Policy discusses the collection, use, sharing and security of personal information on the Company’s website and mobile applications. Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify an individual. Personal information includes your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. By visiting the Company’s website, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.

#### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect information from you when you register on our website or fill out our forms. When ordering or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number.

#### WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  2. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  3. To send periodic emails to you.
  4. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or address other requests or questions.

#### HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit or access your personal information. However, the Company cannot guarantee that any personal information transmitted to its website will be 100% secure. In the event that there is a security breach of any of our users’ personal information, the Company will immediately notify its users of such, and will work to quickly cure the breach.

#### DO WE USE COOKIES?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We may use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.  In addition, the Company may collect and store information such as your device’s IP address, the browser type, your location and the URLs that are referenced in your interaction. These items may be collected and stored in order to enhance and improve the Company’s website. We do not knowingly allow other parties to collect personal information about your online activities when you use our website and services.

#### DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### THIRD PARTY LINKS

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### MAILING LIST AND NEWSLETTER

By registering to the site, mailing list or to the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Application. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Application or after performing a purchase.

#### ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### SHARING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH AFFILIATES AND RELATED PARTIES

The Company may share certain personal information with our affiliates and related parties to enhance their websites and services. In addition, the Company may share non-personally identifiable information with select third parties for advertising purposes. Furthermore, companies that provide services to the Company may have limited access to your personal information.

#### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

The Company is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to our website. These links are purely for informational purposes only. Please note that when you click on these linked sites you are clicking onto another website, and that linked website may collect personally identifiable information about you. We do not control the collection or use of such information and the practices of those websites are not covered by this Policy. Accordingly, we do not endorse, approve or hold ourselves responsible for the privacy policies, terms of use or information gathering practices of any site that you may link to and/or from our website. Thus, our Policy does not apply to those linked sites. We encourage you to obtain and read the privacy statements of these linked websites as they may differ from ours. Again, these links are purely for informational purposes only and Company does not approve, endorse or control any such other website’s content and/or practices or policies.

#### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

The content and services provided through Company is intended for a general audience. Company does not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent, except as permitted by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. If you are a parent who consents to the collection of personal information from your child, you agree that your child may use all of our services and that we may collect, use, and disclose your child’s personal information consistent with this Policy.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this privacy statement, we will revise the “last updated” date at the bottom of this statement.

#### YOUR CONSENT TO THIS POLICY

By using our website, you consent to this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Company’s website.  We reserve the right to amend, modify or otherwise update this Policy at any time, so visitors are encouraged to review this Policy from time to time. Your continued use of the Company’s website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean your acceptance of those changes.

#### CONTACT/QUESTIONS

If you have any questions about this Policy, the practices of our website, or your dealings with our website you can contact 1 Method Center: info [at] methodtreatment [dot] com

If you wish to be removed from our database, please let us know by sending an e-mail notification to info [at] methodtreatment [dot] com and indicating that you would like to unsubscribe.

Effective: April 15, 2019
